Guide to the Records of the Harmonie Club 1852-1995 (Bulk 1860 - 1935) MS 282
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII: Portrait Books, 1910-1915
  The two portrait books were compiled by Frank C. Baker and are composed of photographs of the Harmonie Club Members. One hundred fifty-nine of these portraits were taken by Alman & Co. and the remaining forty-nine are of unknown provenance. Each page of the volume has several photograph windows mounted with the name of each member below their image. Volume One contains an alphabetic index of the members with page numbers as the photos are not arranged in the same manner. The second volume continues the page numbering from the first and is encompassed in Volume One's index.
  - Portraits of Members Volume One, 1910 (Offsite-box 35, Volume 94)
  - Portraits of Members Volume Two, 1912 (Offsite-box 36, Volume 95)
  - Temporary Portfolio of Member Portraits, 1915 (Offsite-box 37, Volume 96)
- Series VIII: Photographs and Ephemera, 1893-1981
  Scope and Contents
  This series include photographs (mainly groups portraits) and loose ephemera, such as menus and invitations, along with a few architectural drawings from a planned 1981 renovation.
  - Menus and other ephemera, 1893, 1914, undated (Offsite-box 38, Volume 97)
  - Menus and other ephemera, 1903, 1930, undated (Box Oversize small)
  - Photographs, undated (Offsite-box 38, Volume 97)
  - Mounted Photographs (2 folders), 1913, undated (Box Oversize small)
  - Banquet Photographs (Folder Oversize small)
  - Architectural Drawings, 1981 (Box Oversize small)
- Series IX: Publications, 1952, 1963-1965
  This series includes copies of the club's newsletter, ""The Harmonie," which was published from 1963 to 1965. Also included are two copies of One Hundred Years, a history of the club from its founding in 1852 until the 1950's.
  - "The Harmonie", 1963 - 1965 (Offsite-box 38, Volume 97)
  - One hundred years, 1852-1952: the Harmonie Club. (Offsite-box 33, Volume 98, 99)